Guide to the Sheri Martinelli Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 1999 Acquisition, 1905-1993; 114.5; (127 boxes)+ 13 art, 1 broadside, 1 roll
  - Audiocassettes and Microcassettes, 1979-1993; Series VI; 78; (78 boxes)
    - Audiocassettes
      - "P anwer to letter #1-2", 1989 June 16; 2 (Box 132)
      - "T/case", undated; 1
      - "Case read law Bk reference to", undated; 1
      - "House ugh(s)", undated; 1
      - "Chatter to Eva Monday," #1-3", 1993 July 5; 3
      - "Tuesday 7/6/93 Eva", 1993 July 6; 1
      - "T.V. catches", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "P/about 11/4/88 Noon 2/SM", 1988 November 4; 1
      - "L/R/Side 1 t/Luna Padre Songs", undated; 1
      - "On tape 8/31/89", 1989 August 31; 1
      - "P/", undated; 1
      - "Church 6/15/89 phone call time to P", undated; 1
      - "a day in t/life of SM's "American Education", undated; 1
      - "P t/trip Sunday 6/10/90", 1990 June 10; 1
      - "Moon from P", undated; 1
      - "1/16/90 notes/tape on tape", 1990 January 16; 1
      - "talk? January 14-15 or so, 1990", undated; 1
      - #2, undated; 1 (Box 133)
      - "EP tape/on tape", undated; 1
      - "Squeeks", undated; 1
      - "Answer P/letters 5/13/89 erase to vague", 1989 May 13; 1
      - "On tape Tuesday with lawn cashier scene with garage studs 6/27/89 T/F", 1989 June 27; 1
      - "Was on tape", undated; 1
      - "P/Sunday June 18, 1989 fury fr. perception talk across st.", 1989 June 18; 1
      - "To self as to why of It #2", undated; 1
      - "Scott", undated; 1
      - "T/case Gladys scene 12/17/88 H", 1988 December 17; 1
      - "Willi 10/10/88 Mor #2", 1988; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Lady Yugoslavia", undated; 1
      - "T/Madonna of Medugorje", undated; 1
      - "Original for t/young dreamers 7/25/89", 1989 July 25; 1
      - "Copy of JAZ tape", undated; 1
      - "P/T/letter", undated; 1
      - "P-hear to select 1/27/90 Sat", 1990 January 7; 1
      - "as T/experience takes place 1/22/90", 1990 January 22; 1
      - "P/wild geese", undated; 1
      - "JAZ", undated; 1 (Box 134)
      - "Camille Claudel artist", undated; 1
      - "First attempt only a bit", undated; 1
      - "P letter after long time Monday 11/6/89", 1989 November 6; 1
      - "Eva", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "DRN also/Joie Day", undated; 1
      - "Begins for St/M and Bird folio St/", undated; 1
      - "P/", undated; 1
      - "Talk (birthday) 1/17/90", 1990 January 17; 1
      - "Paintings", undated; 1
      - [Unlabelled], undated; 2
      - "10 to 5 November 1, 1988", 1988 November 1; 1
      - "Sharon Moon", undated; 1
      - "1 off t/mach 12/9/88", 1988 December 9; 1
      - "2 from mach tape 12/9/88", 1988 December 9; 1
      - "P/6 am Tuesday April 11/89 vidit ideas papers ideas #1", 1989 April 11; 1
      - "#2", undated; 1
      - "From T/#1", undated; 1
      - "P re visit", undated; 1 (Box 135)
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "#1", undated; 1
      - "Teasing dog (?) Monday 10/5/93 PM x#1 scream/teasing dogs to bark", 1993 October 5; 1
      - "x#2", undated; 1
      - "Zuni fourth world", undated; 1
      - "TV Indian American dance", undated; 1
      - "Sex Ed. new/letters/EP Wash time Monday June 19, 1989", 1989 June 19; 1
      - "Monday, June 19, 1989", 1989 June 19; 1
      - "EP auntie uncle 10/15/93", 1993 October 15; 1
      - "In place Sunday after W and company visit Saturday 1/8/89", 1989 January 8; 1
      - "P?", undated; 1
      - "P/1", undated; 1
      - "P listen to last/est one 2", undated; 1
      - "P third", undated; 1
      - "G/feels like paranoia 11/4/88 noon: Friday/ t talk", 1988 November 4; 1
      - "Dreams SM on tape Sanyo", undated; 1
      - "Dreams/gov", undated; 1
      - "T/Power of Myth/Joseph Campbell excerpts/ideas etc.", undated; 1
      - "Play and don't know if A or B Bud and T/cards the time", undated; 1 (Box 136)
      - "Notes to self xy #2", undated; 1
      - "Martin Sunday 7/23/89", 1989 July 23; 1
      - "to self xy #1 7/22/89 continued to xy#2", 1989 July 22; 1
      - "Starting a tape for M Thursday April Monday", undated; 1
      - "EP thoughts at night, batteries slow/ no good listen and copy over", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 4
      - "HI/1," broken tape, undated; 1
      - "H1/#4," broken tape, undated; 1
      - "S + Mao," broken tape, undated; 1
      - Unlabeled, broken tape, undated; 2
      - "2:18," broken tape, undated; 1
      - Astral Sounds broken tapes, 1973; 2
      - "Shamrock and Lela, 8/8/83," broken tape, 1983 August 8; 1
      - "Joe Gould," Ag/86," broken tape, 1986 August; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
    - Microcassettes
      - "Erase? hear 1 more time", undated; 1 (Box 137)
      - On tape and talk/track re D'p'e(ies) etc., undated; 1
      - Notes SM and house, T/Harp song end, undated; 1
      - "Fone mate out and note when fixed mon; note re: cant Klunic vour & sue if am ill; ends on she hre it child, 92=@beg is rest of sisters whelp", undated; 1
      - "H need", 1992 December 23; 1
      - "Was on tape and is about T/case took off to read Rolf Graves", 1992 December 28; 1
      - "Talk Maria, wed", 1992 November 25; 1
      - "I/Pman violin original", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "#1 street P'man SM/ #2 Sun 23-Mon 24", undated; 1
      - "#3 cubs", undated; 1
      - "re 14 cubs", undated; 1
      - "Erased", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "St/M", undated; 1
      - "for authority on here / H J2", 1987 August 30; 1
      - "Homer J2", undated; 1
      - "#4 Ag w + J 25/26", undated; 1
      - "#1 Auto+1YP", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Virgil Dodson reading to SM", 1991 October 7; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Olga 1 HR slow 1.2 keep", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Orig Van", undated; 1
      - "Sl", undated; 1
      - "G-@ time m/visit Friday", 1991 October 25; 1
      - "G & M", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "1.2 G/S", undated; 1
      - "On tape", undated; 1
      - "1.2", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Erase M/G", 1992 June 5; 1
      - "Strange voice", 1992 June 12; 1
      - "gd 3 wish cycle/moon/Scholer job talk", undated; 1
      - "Cayce 3 states", undated; 1
      - "Thrones", 1985; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "St. Noise war and talk cycle", undated; 1
      - "G or D fruits cycle noise nite etc. erase", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Side 1 and 2 M/G/J/S +?", undated; 1
      - [Illegible], undated; 1
      - "Records, mind states, genius", undated; 1
      - "Delta H 4th July 92", 1992 July 4; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
  - Reel-to-Reel Recordings, 1954-1976; Series VII; 5.83; (7 boxes)
    Boxes 138-144 (reel to reel tapes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information
    - "Free", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes (Box 138)
    - "BB", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Green door (Golden Arm) and (Stan Kenton) and (J+Kari), DD", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Recorded April 17, 1954 speed 7 1/2 Side II 4 freshmen and 4 trombones Side I Men with Golden Arm/Sunday September 16, 1956, E", 1954-1956; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "H", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "B", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "James Love- II, Dixie land-I", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes (Box 139)
    - "t/selected version G's trip 4/4/72 t/field scene after G's trip", 1972; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Long wordy original, a cont. fr another tape, full side and half back on parking lot and relatives", 1971; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Side A-Green Door, Billy May and mess at end", 1971; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Charles Bukowski, reading in keeping Sheri", 1961 August 24; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "10:15 a.m. Mon April 17/78", 1978; 1; reel to reel tapes (Box 140)
    - "Drive tape", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Hero stuck" [illegible], undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "SM son[ou] keep-erase-bits", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Wednesday October 17, 1973; October 1973 analysis SM #1, waitress", 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Analysis SM 2", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "October 5, 1972 Friday, memoirs da [illegible] gor, read chron Sybil Zilenski", 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Begin first Hiawatha reading", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "T/Lis. D", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "She/SM poem Turq. Hotel", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "TQ Howl", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Up to May and before Sat 4- Mayor A. Half Moon Bay-FBI", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Gordon Good Flower/ McQN M.A. and Saturday May 4 1974", 1974 May 4; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Tierny Tape 3.10.72", 1972 March 10; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Guns", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Type scene 12/19/1973", 1973 December 19; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 3; reel to reel tapes
    - "t/very first tape, keep-nothing on side 2 this 6/24/71", 1971 June 24; 1; reel to reel tapes (Box 141)
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Tape one 1-A 3/22, Dav Gor policy, Delta/art/punks, Sheri copy on file and one tape of Cadmus Line and half moon and skipped B/art section", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Tape 2 Tape 1-A picks up half moon pie at end Dav gor tape 1 also B's art on front skipped half pie moon (end of) SM copy on file", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Eve", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Copy/Eve", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Ind. music taken off of large machine", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "J + J, Eva H's, Xtra copy", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "First side about 3/4's, first copy SM's tape taken in Montana near Lame Deer 1965 Summer with Sioux Peyote Dance and Arapaho's, Sheri at end", 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Side #1 + 2: Tape taken in Montana near Lame Deer, 1965 Summer with Sioux Peyote Dance", 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Last part Indian Dance and song of T/D's tape and back tape notes #2 4/D testing singing? Down over way", 1965; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Fr poetry entirely owls made on large fr. sm tape 1/27/76", 1976 January 27; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Tested Thursday June 5/75 appears clear and to belong here-time it. T.V. Ind movies film blank prob erase", 1975 June; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "#1 B+N H[P] 1973 at Yale University comments SM", 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "#2 B+N H[P] at Yale University comments SM", 1973; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "B+N H[P] at Yale University, no comments by SM, stratight copy", 1973; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Owls at end s/2 Vogue SP and EP mem[our] etc", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Mr. Clark Ind movies and SM?", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes (Box 142)
    - "Copy vac tape", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 2; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 6; reel to reel tapes
    - "Copy 1 for Eva, R/B/art lesson 1/ and Rev (t/goat) shrieking Lesson 2/ and wolves being hunted by helicopter lesson 3/add trailor of "art by SM etc. (I did but good) ", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Erase 1", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 3; reel to reel tapes
    - "Weekend talks against negative vibes fuse blew ot/o/a dog", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "250! 3/99 health tape", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "J. Ellen", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Shamrock backwards", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [From: T. David Horton to S.M. Lee], [1971]; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "H tape", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes (Box 143)
    - "H second", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "EP/90th First recording by sea edge/ W/2 versions of T/Em Bronte cold in t/ground", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Second EP/90th not so good cut short", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Rounds no use", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - [Unlabeled], undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "T/first part for Bill T/re-read T/rest for T/B.T./ shell second side EP ESP/ last part for Mary T/opera G's opera, copy for B.T.", [1971]; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "EP 4 BT", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Planes at creek and Friday", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Vivaldi and other recorded music", 1975 June 26; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Delta #26", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Ret R/ad Ray + guns Baker Sen/R/ at end original", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Lawyer original", 1975 September 9; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Curtis Ind T.V. S.M. and music", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Turk howl", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Music and sirens for Turq. howling", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Libers over and over, Sheri +.", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "Liber on FT", undated; 1; reel to reel tapes
    - "G's trip", 1972 April 7; 3; reel to reel tapes (Box 144)
    - "Art", undated; 3; reel to reel tapes
- August 1999 Acquisition Addition, 1956-1961; 0.21; (1 box)
  Correspondence, notes, and printed material related to Sheri Martinelli.
  - Letters, notes, printed ephemera, clippings, by or relating to Sheri Martinelli, 1956-1961; 3 (Box 146)
- Printed Material, 1954-1976
  - Accent, A Quarterly of New Literature. New York New Directions Press, 1956 (Box A)
  - Agenda. London; Poets and Painters Press, 4 issues, 1959-1962
  - American Astrology. Volume 30, Number II, Larchmont, New York: Clancy Publications, 1962
  - Book of the Dead. London: British Museum, 1920
  - The Braham Episode. Germany: Kottmeirer and Kostetzky, 1962
  - Breakthru, Art. Religion. Science. Philosophy., 1960
  - Collected Early Poems by Ezra Pound. New York: New Directions Publishing, 1976
  - Connolly, Thomas, Ezra Pound's "Near Perigord": The Background of a Poem. Reprint from Comparative Literature., 1956
  - Current. Issue 29 [2 Copies], 30, 31, 34 [2 Copies], 35 [2 Copies] Provincetown: Four Winds Press, undated
  - Goullart, Peter, Forgotten Kingdom. London: John Murray, 1955
  - Ede, H.S., Savage Messiah Gaudier- Brzeska. New York: The Literary Guild, 1931
  - Hudson Review, 4 copies
  - Kuan-Tzu
  - Liriche Amorose, Degli Antichi Egiziani. Milan: All'Insegna Del Pesce D'Oro, 1955
  - Massime, Degli Antichi Egiziani. Milan; All'Insegna Del Pesce D'Oro, 1954
  - Nine. A Magazine of Poetry and Criticism, 9 issues, 1949-1956
  - The Paris Review 28, 1962
  - Analects, translated by Ezra Pound (Box B)
  - Pounds' Artists
  - Confucius The Unwobbling Pivot of the Great Digest. Translated by Ezra Pound. Washington D.C.: Square $ Series [2 copies], undated
  - Ezra Pound at Seventy A booklet with quotes from Auden, Hemingway, Eliot. New York: New Directions, two copies
  - Richardson, John, A collection of his poetry., undated
  - Semina Two. A pasted together leaflet of poetry by various writers n.d.
  - Shenandoah, The Washington and Lee University Review, 1954
  - Mark Twain Journal [2 Issues], 1954-58
  - Pound, Ezra, Personae, The Collected Poems. New York: James Laughlin for New Directions, undated